thephilippinestimes.com 2019-06-15

# Bollywood Charcha

## **Privacy Policy**

This Privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for The Philippines Times.com. We are glad to see your interest and trust in our website. You need not to submit any kind of personal information in order to browse the website but policies can be changed anytime.

**What information we gather about you?**

  * Automatic Information: We receive and store several types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, many websites use “Cookies” and obtain a certain type of information when you access the website on the web browser or other content served by on behalf of the website on other websites.
  * The information you provide us: We store any information that you enter on our website. We use the information just to respond to your requests, improving our website and communication with you.
  * Other websites links: The content on this website may contain links to other external websites.

**What do we do with your personal information?**

Personal information that our users provide us is very important for us and we understand its terms so we do not share such information with anyone else. We only share it in the following circumstances:

  * In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation of the our terms and provisions
  * To implement or entail terms and conditions and privacy policies
  * To protect our character, assets and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users
  * We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief because it is necessary to disclose such info to counter court orders or miscellaneous legal processes.
  * In case of transferring or selling the website to other company so user’s info will be transferred too.

**About IP addresses?**

We might use your personal information or data we collect in connection with your use of ThePhilippinesTimes in order to implement, prevent, investigate, identity theft, fraud, or multiple accounts to prevent making abusive comments. In order to get the such information we may collect data like IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), which browser you are using to visit Mytimesnow.com like Google Chrome plus we also capture time taken by you to surf on ThePhilippinesTimes and the number of pages you visited on the site.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are basically small text files, given ID tags that are stored on your computer's browser directory. Cookies are created when you use your browser to visit a website that uses cookies to keep track of your movements within the site. A cookie can be of two types- the first is which expires when you close the browser and the second stays in your computer until you delete it manually. So like another company our readers will get cookies by us or by companies which are running their ads on our website. Cookies can help us and advertisers to analyze and identify users on our website and it also helps us to serve content to match your preferences.

**Policy update:**

**In case we change or update our privacy policies we will inform you by posting it on our website or keep visiting our website.**

If you have any concern about privacy please send us a mail at    so that we can help you with the problem.
